<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorials on Ypertex Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ypertex.com/tags/tutorials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutorials on Ypertex Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Some rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ypertex.com/tags/tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Unhide Virtual Network Adapters in Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://blog.ypertex.com/articles/unhide-virtual-network-adapters-windows-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ypertex.com/articles/unhide-virtual-network-adapters-windows-10/</guid>
      <description>If you ever have installed a virtualization platform like VMware Workstation or Oracle Virtualbox on a Windows 10 box, you might have noticed a different behavior since recent releases (i.e. release 1903): All the virtual network adapters introduced by VMware Workstation et al. don&#39;t appear anymore in the &amp;ldquo;Network and Sharing Center&amp;rdquo; and other parts of Windows.
I assume that for the majority of users, these adapters showing up in all possible places of the OSjust like regular network interfaces caused more confusion than it was helpful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enabling JumpCloud on Unsupported Linux Systems</title>
      <link>https://blog.ypertex.com/articles/jumpcloud-on-unsupported-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ypertex.com/articles/jumpcloud-on-unsupported-linux/</guid>
      <description>If you followed the articles on this blog you know that I have a lot of love1, 2for JumpCloud.
However, there is a JumpCloud limitation that bugs me a little: It refuses to run on some Linux-based systems like Proxmox Virtual Environment or Openmediavault even though it officially supports the underlying Linux version.
Fortunately, there&#39;s a way around that limitation that I&#39;d like to share with you in this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Advertise Subnets to Upstream Routers with OPNsense and ARP</title>
      <link>https://blog.ypertex.com/articles/advertise-subnet-with-opnsense-arp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ypertex.com/articles/advertise-subnet-with-opnsense-arp/</guid>
      <description>Splitting stuff is hard enough, but how do you move away the part that you just split off? (Image: Pablo Heimplatz)  Today was the first time that I needed to split one IPv4 subnet into two and forward the second half to somewhere else—without the ability to configure the upstream gateway. It took me a while to figure out how to achieve this with an OPNsense firewall as my router.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Around the JumpCloud Curl Error 22</title>
      <link>https://blog.ypertex.com/articles/jumpcloud-curl-error-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ypertex.com/articles/jumpcloud-curl-error-22/</guid>
      <description>Introducing JumpCloud In case you have not yet heard about JumpCloud: It is a cloud service that leverages user directories like Active Directory, Office 365, and G Suite (previously known as Google Apps) for Single Sign On in web apps and clients. My favorite feature of JumpCloud is its lightweight agent: Installing this little piece of software on Linux, MacOS and Windows clients and servers enables you and your directory users to log into these machines with your directory credentials.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>