<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design on Ypertex Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ypertex.com/tags/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design on Ypertex Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Some rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ypertex.com/tags/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Unhide Virtual Network Adapters in Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://blog.ypertex.com/articles/unhide-virtual-network-adapters-windows-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ypertex.com/articles/unhide-virtual-network-adapters-windows-10/</guid>
      <description>If you ever have installed a virtualization platform like VMware Workstation or Oracle Virtualbox on a Windows 10 box, you might have noticed a different behavior since recent releases (i.e. release 1903): All the virtual network adapters introduced by VMware Workstation et al. don&amp;rsquo;t appear anymore in the &amp;ldquo;Network and Sharing Center&amp;rdquo; and other parts of Windows.
I assume that for the majority of users, these adapters showing up in all possible places of the OS just like regular network interfaces caused more confusion than it was helpful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Your Way to Success</title>
      <link>https://blog.ypertex.com/articles/test-your-way-to-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ypertex.com/articles/test-your-way-to-success/</guid>
      <description>Assumptions Can Be Helpful &amp;hellip; Think a moment about the assumptions on which you rely to get through a typical day in your life. Your routine on any given workday is probably based on the following basic assumptions, just to name a few:
 Your alarm will wake you up in time The transportation for your commute will function properly There will be the usual opportunities to get food and drinks throughout the day  Simply assuming these things—rather than verifying them one by one each and every day—successfully gets you through your workday routine most of the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Making of the Ypertex Logo</title>
      <link>https://blog.ypertex.com/articles/the-making-of-the-ypertex-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ypertex.com/articles/the-making-of-the-ypertex-logo/</guid>
      <description>For a blog claiming to primarily write about design (according to its current tag line “Design, Technology, Future”), I have yet to do so after three articles. Let me change that today—but before I write about other people’s designs, I would like to first promote my credibility and address one of my own designs: this blog’s logo.
This article explains how I generally approach new designs using the example of the Ypertex logo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>